<data>
<text0><![CDATA[<font color="#980101"><B>Root Cause Analysis:</B> Summary</font>]]></text0>
<text1><![CDATA[<B>Home Base, Outside North Gate</B>]]></text1>
<text2><![CDATA[<B>Derailment of train cars carrying industrial chemicals</B>]]></text2>
<text3><![CDATA[<B>BE Team Lead</B>]]></text3>
<text4><![CDATA[<p align="center"><B>1310</B></p>]]></text4>
<text5><![CDATA[<B>BE Team Member</B>]]></text5>

<heading><![CDATA[<B>Navigation and Features</B>]]></heading>


<!-- Option menu -->
<text6><![CDATA[The Options Menu appears at the lower left corner of each screen and allows you to access key features of this tool. Click each button to learn more.]]></text6>

<text7><![CDATA[<B>Help</B>]]></text7>
<text8><![CDATA[Selecting Help will open a document containing Frequently Asked Questions (FAQs) and the answers to those questions.]]></text8>

<text9><![CDATA[<B>Equip and Ref</B>]]></text9>
<text10><![CDATA[The Equipment Information and References screen provides a directory of information about pieces of equipment and key reference items that are referred to throughout the given scenario. This screen is available throughout each scenario on any page that is not testing knowledge pertaining to equipment or references listed. ]]></text10>

<text11><![CDATA[<B>Player Info</B><br><br>Each scenario and assessment is scored according to your responses to specific questions or situations. The Player Info screen provides a way for you to review your progress and identify areas of strengths and weaknesses according to listed competencies for that assessment.<br><br>The questions you will be asked represent both questions that assess RSV objectives and questions that include some degree of subjectivity. If the question is <B>not</B> tied to an RSV objective, it is not scored and has no impact on the successful completion of your verification package.<br><br>If the question <B>is</B> tied to an RSV objective, those points are allocated to one or more of the core competencies displayed in your Player Info screen as Objective Points. Your end of assessment scores are based on the points you earn from objective-based questions only.<br><br>By selecting Player Info, you can view your scores as a percentage of the total Objective Points available in the assessment for each of the core competency areas listed. ]]></text11>

<text12><![CDATA[<B>Audio Transcript</B>]]></text12>
<text13><![CDATA[Audio is a key element used throughout this tool. When audio is played or available, a corresponding audio transcript can be displayed by selecting the Audio Transcript button from the Options Menu.]]></text13>
<text14><![CDATA[Audio transcripts do not automatically appear when audio is playing and the button is not active unless there is audio playing. You must select the Audio Transcript button from the menu again to remove the transcript from the screen. For this page, select another button on the Options Menu to continue.]]></text14>

<text15><![CDATA[<U>Narrator:</U> As you've already seen, audio is a key element used throughout this tool.  The audio and audio transcript for this page functions a little differently than usual because you're learning about the features of the program.<br><br>During the Knowledge Assessments and Scenarios, when audio is played or available, a corresponding audio transcript can be displayed by selecting the Audio Transcript button from the Options Menu.<br><br>Audio transcripts do not automatically appear when audio is playing and the button is not active unless there is audio playing. Usually, you must select the Audio Transcript button from the menu again to remove the transcript from the screen. For this page, select another button on the Options Menu to continue.]]></text15>


<!-- Prompt Bar -->
<text16><![CDATA[<B>Prompt Bar</B>]]></text16>
<text17><![CDATA[Specific directions for the page you're currently on are located at the lower-center of your screen, in the prompt bar.]]></text17>
<text18><![CDATA[Because there are many different types of screens and question formats you'll see throughout the scenarios, paying attention to the instructions in the prompt bar is very important.]]></text18>

<!-- Points and Progress Bar -->
<text19><![CDATA[<B>Progress Bar</B>]]></text19>
<text20><![CDATA[In the lower right of the screen, you will see a progress bar. The bar fills in with color as you progress through each Knowledge Assessment and Scenario.]]></text20>
<text21><![CDATA[]]></text21>
<text22><![CDATA[]]></text22>

<!-- Exit -->
<text23><![CDATA[<B>Exit</B>]]></text23>
<text24><![CDATA[Selecting the Exit button allows you to exit the program. You will be prompted when you select Exit to ensure that you are ready to leave the program. It's important to close the program this way so that your scores and progress are saved properly.]]></text24>
<text25><![CDATA[If you exit the program in the middle of a Knowledge Assessment, the data will NOT be saved and you will need to begin the assessment again when you return.]]></text25>
<text26><![CDATA[If you exit the program before you have completed a scenario, you will be immediately returned to the beginning of the portion of the scenario in which you are working. For example, if the screen title indicates you are in Part I of the scenario and you exit the course, the system will bookmark your location as the <B>beginning</B> of Part I, even if you're on the last page of that portion. All progress and points earned while in that portion, past the point of the bookmark, will be lost upon exiting.]]></text26>
<text27><![CDATA[Therefore, it is highly recommended that if you <B>must</B> exit the program before completing a scenario that you exit immediately after you enter a new portion or "Part" of the scenario.]]></text27>


<!-- Life line -->
<text28><![CDATA[<B>Lifeline Button</B>]]></text28>
<text29><![CDATA[The Lifeline is a feature that provides specific assistance about the question or task you're working on at that point. Lifelines are represented by the appearance of an animated green button and an audio reminder that the Lifeline is standing by. Lifelines are provided periodically throughout each scenario to simulate situations when you may have to consult references or seek reach-back support during a real response.<br><br>A Lifeline can be audio-driven or can display a document that should be helpful in answering the question or series of questions.<br><br>It is highly recommended that you take advantage of Lifeline support. There is no penalty for using a Lifeline when one is provided.]]></text29>

<!-- MAP -->
<text30><![CDATA[<B>Highlighted Items</B>]]></text30>
<text31><![CDATA[Highlighted or selectable text or graphics can trigger a number of actions, such as:
<ul><li>Playing audio</li><li>Playing animation</li><li>Displaying text or another graphic</li><li>Navigating within a scenario</li><li>Interacting with the characters in a scenario</li></ul><br>Selectable items are usually highlighted in a turquoise blue color and, once triggered, will remain highlighted for later reference.<br><br>When blue highlighting is not provided, the prompt or other triggers on the screen will indicate which item or items should be selected. The flashing red phone on this page is an example of an exception to the use of blue highlighting.<br><br>If a larger image or a document is displayed from a selectable item, an X in the upper right hand corner can close the image or document when you're done reviewing the item.]]></text31>


<text32><![CDATA[<B>Options Menu</B>]]></text32>

<transcript_text><![CDATA[Default Transcript]]></transcript_text>

</data>