<data>
<text0><![CDATA[<font color="#980101"><B>Root Cause Analysis:</B> Summary</font>]]></text0>
<text1><![CDATA[<B>Home Base, Outside North Gate</B>]]></text1>
<text2><![CDATA[<B>Derailment of train cars carrying industrial chemicals</B>]]></text2>
<text3><![CDATA[Selection Point Text]]></text3>

<text4><![CDATA[<B>Menu Functionality</B>]]></text4>

<text5><![CDATA[Upon selecting a Knowledge Assessment or Scenario, you will notice an animated red, circular selection point at one of the locations on the base. Click on the selection point for more information.]]></text5>

<text6><![CDATA[Select Options/Audio Transcript to view the audio transcription. Select the button again to hide the transcript.]]></text6>

<text7><![CDATA[<B>Selection Points</B>]]></text7>

<text8><![CDATA[A red selection point represents an available assessment. When you roll over any selection point with your mouse, you'll see a label indicating what that point represents. You'll need to click on the selection point with your mouse to receive more information and to enter the assessment.]]></text8>

<text9><![CDATA[Click on the School House selection point now to learn more.]]></text9>

<text10><![CDATA[Each of your Knowledge Assessments will be accessed through the School House location on the base.  Read the information on this screen to learn more. When you are finished, select Return. ]]></text10>

<text11><![CDATA[<B>Assessment Access</B>]]></text11>

<text12><![CDATA[You will be able to access Knowledge Assessments through the School House location on the base, and Scenario-based Assessments at indicated locations.<br><br>A passing score for any assessment is 70% or higher. If you do not pass the first attempt at an assessment, the assessment remains available for you to try again.]]></text12>

<text13><![CDATA[<B>Scenario Information</B>]]></text13>

<text14><![CDATA[When you click on a scenario selection point, a popup orientation box will appear that provides you with information relevant to that scenario. You can then choose whether to enter the scenario or return to the menu.  
When you enter each scenario, you will randomly be assigned one of three roles: BE Team Lead, BE Team Member, or Exercise Evaluator. After your role is determined, you will be required to answer<br>scenario-related questions from the perspective you have been assigned.<br><br>For example, if you're assigned as a BE Team Lead, you may be asked to determine in what order your team should complete identified activities or if the actions your team members took were correct.<br><br>If you are assigned the Team Member role, you'll be asked to answer questions using provided information or situation-specific details. While in this role, you may be sent down several paths to give you the opportunity to play the part of multiple team members.<br><br>If you're assigned the Exercise Evaluator role, you'll be asked to watch movies that represent the actions and decisions of the BE Team. While listening to and watching a segment of one of the other two roles, you will determine whether you agree with the answers selected by the team. If you disagree with the answers selected, you'll be given an opportunity to go through the segment yourself and select the answers you feel are correct. You may review the questions and the selections made by the BE Team in the movie by using the player bar functions to pause, play, or rewind the movie.]]></text14>

<text15><![CDATA[<B>Base Post Office</B>]]></text15>
<text16><![CDATA[<B>Suspicious box leaking an oily substance</B>]]></text16>
<text17><![CDATA[<B>BE Team Member</B>]]></text17>
<text18><![CDATA[<B>1200</B>]]></text18>

</data>