<data>
<text0><![CDATA[<font color="#980101"><B>Root Cause Analysis:</B> Summary</font>]]></text0>
<text1><![CDATA[<B>Question Types</B>]]></text1>
<text2><![CDATA[This verification tool includes several types of questions that are used to assess your knowledge and skills related to the RSV objectives. There are four primary question types in this program, but the instructions may vary slightly based on the content of the question. You are only allowed one attempt per question so be sure to read the instructions carefully. Once you click “DONE” you will not be able to back up to the previous screen to change your selection.]]></text2>

<!-- popup 01 -->
<text3><![CDATA[<B>Multiple Choice</B>]]></text3>
<text4><![CDATA[Multiple Choice questions generally include a question and a group of possible answers. For this question, type there is only <B><I>one </I></B>correct answer.]]></text4>
<text5><![CDATA[The answer choices for the Multiple Choice questions are preceded by a <B>round</B> selection button.]]></text5>

<!-- popup 02 -->

<text6><![CDATA[<B>Multiple Answer</B>]]></text6>
<text7><![CDATA[Multiple Answer questions generally include a question and a group of possible answers. For this question type there are <B><I>multiple</I></B> correct answers that you should select.]]></text7>
<text8><![CDATA[You will be able to quickly identify a Multiple Answer question because the answer choices are preceded by a <I><B>square</B></I> selection button.]]></text8>

<!-- popup 03 -->

<text9><![CDATA[<B>Drag and Drop</B>]]></text9>
<text10><![CDATA[Drag and Drop questions generally include a question or statement and a series of items that can be moved to specific locations on the screen. This question type is often used to assess your ability to place steps in the proper sequence or to select items from a group of possible answers. Follow the specific directions on the screen when you're asked to answer a Drag and Drop question.]]></text10>

<!-- popup 04 -->

<text11><![CDATA[<B>Click Grid</B>]]></text11>
<text12><![CDATA[Click Grid questions generally include a question or statement and a series of items that should be matched to appropriate columns. ]]></text12>
<text13><![CDATA[Follow the specific directions on the screen for this type of question.]]></text13>

<transcript_text><![CDATA[Default Transcript]]></transcript_text>
</data>