<data>
<text0><![CDATA[<font color="#980101"><B>Root Cause Analysis:</B> Summary</font>]]></text0>
<text1><![CDATA[<B>Part III:  Interpreting the Findings</B>]]></text1>
<text2><![CDATA[<p align ="center">Cs-137 Health Effects</p>]]></text2>
<text3><![CDATA[<p align ="center">I-131 Health Effects</p>]]></text3>
<text4><![CDATA[<B>Health Effects of Cs-137</B><BR><BR>Cesium-137 is completely absorbed by the lungs, gastrointestinal tract, and wounds. It is soluble in most forms and is treated by metabolism as a potassium analog. Excretion is in urine. Primary toxicity is whole-body irradiation. Deaths due to acute radiation syndrome have occurred.<BR><BR>Like all radionuclides, exposure to radiation from Cesium-137 results in increased risk of cancer. Everyone is exposed to very small amounts of Cesium-137 in soil and water as a result of atmospheric fallout. Exposure to waste materials, from contaminated sites, or from nuclear accidents can result in cancer risks much higher than typical environmental exposures.  If exposures are very high, serious burns, and even death, can result.<BR><BR>Instances of such exposure are very rare. One example of a high-exposure situation would be the mishandling a strong industrial Cesium-137 source. The magnitude of the health risk depends on exposure conditions. These include such factors as strength of the source, length of exposure, distance from the source, and whether there was shielding between you and the source (such as metal plating).]]></text4>
<text5><![CDATA[<B>Health Effects of I-131</B><BR><BR>External exposure to large amounts of I-131 can cause burns to the eyes and on the skin. Internal exposure can affect the thyroid gland. The thyroid gland uses iodine to produce thyroid hormones and cannot distinguish between radioactive iodine and stable (nonradioactive) iodine. <BR><BR>If I-131 were released into the atmosphere, people could ingest it in food products or water, or breathe it in. In addition, if dairy animals consume grass contaminated with I-131, the radioactive iodine will be incorporated into their milk. Consequently, people can receive internal exposure from drinking the milk or eating dairy products made from contaminated milk. <BR><BR>Once inside the body, I-131 will be absorbed by the thyroid gland exposing it to radiation and potentially increasing the risk for thyroid cancer or other thyroid problems. However, once thyroid cancer occurs, treatment with high doses of I-131 may be used to treat it. Doctors also use lower doses of I-131 to treat overactive thyroids. Low doses can reduce activity of the thyroid gland, lowering hormone production in the gland. Doctors must maintain the fine balance between the risks and benefits of using radioactive iodine.]]></text5>

<transcript_text><![CDATA[Default Transcript]]></transcript_text>
</data>